Guide to the Continuing Engineering Education records, 1968-1995 RG0131
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Continuing Engineering Education records
1968-1995
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0131
19 Linear Feet
Collection contains brochures and videotapes.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Continuing Engineering Education.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Continuing Engineering Education Program (CEEP) was part of the School of Engineering and Applied Technology. CEEP began by offering short courses in applied technology to individuals, mostly in the defense establishments, during the 1960s. By 1994, CEEP was offering 500 course per year in engineering and other disciplines including management. In 1994, CEEP joined with the School of Business and Public Management to create the Center for Organized Effectiveness. CEEP has merged with the Center for Professional Development.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains brochures and videotapes. These materials cover the dates 1968-95. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into four series: three are titled Course brochures and one is titled Videotapes.
Continuing education; Engineering; Washington (D.C.); George Washington University
- Course brochures, 1971-1987; RG0131 Series 1; 6.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains course brochures. These items cover the dates 1971-87.
  - Course Brochures, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Binders
  - Course Brochures, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Course Brochures, 1978-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Course Brochures, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Course Brochures, 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Loose Brochures
- Course brochures, 1968-1984; RG0131 Series 2; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  This series contains brochures for off-campus short courses. These items cover the dates 1968-84.
  - Brochures, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brochures, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brochures, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brochures, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brochures, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Brochures, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Brochures, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Brochures, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Course brochures, 1989-1995; RG0131 Series 3; 1 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 3, Box 1)
  This series contains brochures for off-campus short courses. These items cover the dates 1989-95.
- Videotapes, 1987-1992; RG0131 Series 4; 9 Linear feet
  This series contains videotapes. These videos cover the dates 1987-92 and are identified as master copies.
  - Drucker, 02/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Drucker, 09/1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Drucker, 01/1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Drucker, 05/1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Elliot, 11/1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Drucker, 10/1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Drucker, 02/1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ReVelle-Stat Method and QIPNIP, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Deming, 06/1988 - --07/1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hall of Fame, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Kaplan, 03/1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lehman, 10/1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Deming, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Two day
  - Barton, 05/1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Baldrige, 01/1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hudiburg, 01/1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Crosby, 04/1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)